欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
《鬼娃恰吉》前情提要
Previously on"Chucky"...
该死的 这房子还不够邪恶啊
God damn it. This house isn't evil enough.
我们的计划得更宏伟一点
We've gotta think bigger.
要让这房子里做出的决定
Millions have died because of the decisions
造成数以百万的死亡
made inside those walls.
詹妮弗·蒂莉 因一级谋杀
Jennifer Tilly, for the crime of murder in the first degree,
你被判处死刑
you are hereby sentenced to death.
让她成为我的木偶
Fais d’ elle ma marionette!
有什么我能帮到你的吗
- Is there anything I can get for you?
进来的路上我数了一下 有6个警卫
On my way in, I counted six guards.
我需要你做的是 从这些警卫每人手里
What I need from you is to get a single personal item
拿一件私人物品给我
from each one of these guards and bring it to me.
告诉我吧 医生
- Give it to me straight, Doc.
肯定有什么你能做的
There's got to be something you can do.
我是说 我也不会真死啊
I mean, I can' t actually die.
这恐怕需要一个强大到
- It will take an evil of a magnitude
连你都无法包容的邪恶
even you can' t comprehend.
我有点动心
- I' m intrigued.
我也想他
- I miss him too.
你不用想他 爸爸
- You don' t have to miss him, Daddy.
他就在这呢
He' s right there.
一个杀手正觊觎着白宫
There’s a killer stalking the White House,
可你却坚持要开趴
and you' re insisting on throwing a party.
我坚持的是设个陷阱
- I'm insisting on setting a trap.
他们可以做我最后神圣的三件祭品
They can be my last three sacred offerings.
然后我就能摆脱这个诅咒了
And I' ll be free of this curse.
你的衣服可真漂亮
That’ s a nice costume you have there.
是迷路了吗
You lost?
卡洛琳在哪
- Where is Caroline?
-谁是卡洛琳  -我就知道
Who's Caroline? - I knew it.
你跟其他人一样 只是利用我进来而已
You just used me to get inside, just like everyone else.
我真希望能跟你一起去白宫
- I just wish I could go to the White House with you.
等我杀了6个人之后就可以了
- It's just till I kill six people.
很快的
It'll fly by.
丹巴拉 你为什么要抛弃我啊
Damballa! Why have you forsaken me?
我特么要死了
I' m fucking dying!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
作为你们的最高统帅
as your Commander in Chief,
我有责任面对我们在战场上
it is my duty to confront the terrible weight of any loss
遭受的任何损失
that we suffer on the battlefield.
你们许多人都知道
As many of you know,
我和我的家人经历过悲剧
my family and I are no strangers to tragedy.
虽然这是白宫
And while this might be the White House,
但对我和家人来说 这里也是我们的家
for me and my family, it is also home.
我们对昨晚发生在这里的悲剧
We' re devastated
深感悲痛
by the tragedy that unfolded here last night.
爸爸
Daddy.
天 抱歉
God, sorry.
昨晚的大多数嘉宾
Most of the guests last night were also
也是亲密的朋友和同事
close friends and colleagues,
他们把自己的一生
men and women that have dedicated
都奉献给了公共服务
their entire lives to public service- -
爸爸
Daddy.
昨晚的很多宾客
Many of the guests here last night were- -
总统先生
Mr. President?
爸爸 不
Daddy, no.
爸爸 爸爸 不
Daddy. Daddy, no.
爸爸
Daddy.
爸爸 爸爸 爸爸 爸爸
Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, Daddy.
早上好 女士们先生们
- Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
显然 对于总统和第一家庭来说
Obviously, these are very difficult times
这是非常艰难的时刻
for the President and the First Family.
我们恳请大家在他们悲痛的时候尊重他们的隐私
We ask that you respect their privacy as they grieve.
谢谢
Thank you.
第一夫人
Oh, Madam First Lady,
我没想到新闻发布会搞砸了
I didn' t think you were still coming
你还会来
after that debacle of a press conference.
-他只是太累了  -当然啊 你最了解他
- He's tired, is all. - Of course. You know him best.
但是鉴于总统今早的表现
But given the President’ s demeanor this morning,
我不得不问
I have to ask,
你告诉他我们的小计划了吗
did you tell him about our little project?
-我们正在做的清理工作吗  -当然没有
This cleanup we re doing? - Of course not.
詹姆斯完全不知道会发生什么
James doesn't know anything about what' s going on,
而且也不能让他知道
and that's how it' s going to stay.
这种秘密可不好保守
Secrets like that can be hard to keep.
我很清楚
I should know.
当你为了保护家庭
Not when you' re keeping them
和你努力建立起来的一切
to protect your family
就不会保守不住了
and everything you' ve worked to build.
现在 普莱斯先生 你问够了吗
Now, Mr. Pryce, any other questions,
可以轮到我问你问题了吗
or can I ask you some of my own?
你发现了什么
What have you found?
在万圣节那次意外之后
Well, after the mishap on Halloween,
我在特勤局
I did a little digging
和特区警察插手之前
before the Secret Service and D. C. Police
做了一些调查
could get their paws in things.
枝形吊灯不是意外掉下来的
The chandelier didn't fall by accident.
有人松动了螺丝
Someone loosened the bolts.
凶手越来越无所顾忌了
Our killer is getting more brazen.
他越大胆
And the bolder he gets,
我们就越有可能失去对事态的控制
the more we risk losing control of the narrative.
也许是时候改变作战计划了
It might be time to change the game plan.
我们可以给媒体透露些信息
We could feed some of what we know to the media.
我希望你是在开玩笑
- I hope you' re kidding.
我们都深陷其中
We're knee- deep in this.
现在不能透露真相
There’s no exposing the truth now.
如果我们了解内情这事被媒体知道了
If it comes out that we knew something,
我们就会被视为玩忽职守 甚至被视为同谋
we'll look negligent, or worse, complicit.
风险肯定是有的
－ That's certainly a risk.
不行
No.
我要提醒你 唯一保护总统
The only way to protect the President,
我的家人还有我们自己的方法
my family, and ourselves, I'Il remind you,
就是坚持到底
is to push through it.
那你就得看看这个了
- Then there’ s something else you need to see.
那里
There.
看好了
Watch there.
抱歉我不得不这么说
I' m sorry to say this, but
我们要对付的恐怕已超出了之前的想象
we might be dealing with something else entirely.
那个人看着眼熟吗 第一夫人
Does that figure look familiar, Madam First Lady?
不
No.
可能是任何东西 光线的错觉 信号故障
It could be anything- - a trick of light, glitch.
毫无意义
It's meaningless.
你来这是找凶手的 所以给我找到他
You’re here to find a killer, so find him.
嘿 儿子们
Hey, guys?
嗨 爸爸
Hi, Dad.
格兰特 你看见我的书了吗
Grant, have you seen my book?
你感觉怎么样
- How you holding up?
好的不得了
Never been better.
行吧
Right.
嘿 也许等这一切都过去了
Hey, maybe when this is all over,
你可以给我讲讲认识的那个女孩
you can tell me about that girl you' re seeing.
应该用过去式
You should be using the past tense.
这是什么意思
- What is that supposed to mean?
意思就是我们完了
Means it' s over.
她更感兴趣的是我住哪
She was more interested in where I live
还有我爸是谁
and what my dad does for a living.
从来就不是我
She never gave a shit about getting to know me.
嘿 注意语言
Hey, hey, hey, language.
-抱歉了  -亨利 我在车里等你
I' m sorry. - Henry, I Il be in the car.
-抱歉了   -亨利 我在车里等你
I' m sorry. Henry, I'Il be in the car.
嘿 小家伙
Hey, buddy.
过来
Come here for a second.
你还好吗
How are you, pal?
你的娃娃呢
Where’s your doll?
他休息呢
- He's resting.
为什么他要休息
- Why is he resting?
因为他病了
Because he s sick.
病的很重
He's so sick.
我担心他又要死了
I' m afraid he' s gonna die again.
你见过约瑟夫吗
Do you ever see Joseph?
我天天都见到他
- I see him every day.
不 不是那个娃娃
No, not the doll.
真的约瑟夫 你弟弟
The real Joseph, your brother.
你见过他吗
Do you ever see him?
亨利
Henry.
到时间上学了
I think it' s time to go.
嘿 祝你今天过的开心 小家伙
Hey, try and have a good day, OK, buddy?
也许你该休息一下
Maybe you should get some rest.
我想说的是
AII I' m saying is,
我们现在知道有多难接近恰吉了
we saw how hard it was to get to Chucky.
他知道只要他待在白宫里
He knows that as long as he s in the White House,
我们就得按不同的规矩行事
we have to play by different rules.
我管他是在白宫
- It doesn' t matter if he' s in the White House
还是白堡
or a White Castle.
他知道我妹在哪
He knows where my sister is.
我要逼他告诉我
I' m going to make him tell me.
莱克西说的对
Lexy’ s right.
我们的任务都一样
Our job is the same either way.
救下卡洛琳 杀了恰吉
Save Caroline, kill Chucky.
但需要抓紧了
But in a hurry.
如果说万圣节派对预示着未来
If the Halloween party is a sign of what' s to come,
那恰吉就又要杀人了
Chucky' s out for blood.
有件事我想不通
Something doesn't make sense.
我是说 恰吉可以随心所欲的杀人
I mean, Chucky can kill anywhere he wants.
他为什么要搞这些呢
Why is he doing this?
反正不是为了留作纪念
- I don' t think it’ s a commemorative pen set.
我们必须再回去
We have to get back in there.
我这有点麻烦
- Yeah, slight snag.
格兰特现在不太喜欢我
Grant is not my biggest fan at the moment.
他生气了
He was upset.
生气到对我不理不睬
Like, "not answering my texts" upset.
这可不妙啊
- Oh. - This isn't good.
男生怎么都这么脆弱啊
Boys are so fragile.
你们这些家伙都太容易自尊心受伤了
It's all male ego- tripping bullshit with you guys.
你得想办法跟他和好啊
- You have to make it up with him.
他觉得我对他没上心吧
Look, he feels rejected.
只是利用他去参观白宫幕后
He thinks I used him to get a behind- the- scenes tour.
你的确利用了他
You did.
我只想让他知道我一点也不在乎
- I just need to show him that I don' t care at all
他爸是不是总统
that his dad' s the president.
我只在乎我妹妹
I just care about my sister.
所以你觉得能跟他和好吗
So do you think you can fix it with him?
让我想想
- Let's see, can I manage
我能应付一个骄傲 脆弱 受伤
a proud, delicate, wounded teenage boy
又喜欢我的十几岁男孩吗
who' s painfully head- over- heels into me?
我觉得可以
Yeah, I think I got this.
他们又没给我足够的钱干这破事
－ They don' t pay me enough for this shit.
这有什么意义呢
Ah, what’s the point?
刺激感早已消失
Do you ever feel like the thrill is gone?
就好像一切都不再重要了
Like nothing even matters anymore?
我以前就是为杀人而活的
I used to live for this shit.
你在痛苦中死去
You dying in agony,
而我则高兴的看着
me gleefully watching you die in agony.
你无法想象我现在有多失望
- You just can't imagine how disappointing this is for me.
现在我特么还要收拾干净
Now I gotta fucking clean this up.
重大新闻
白宫恐怖事件 十人死亡
我们当时就在场
We were right there,
可还是阻止不了恰吉
and we still couldn' t stop Chucky.
你想听听我的计划吗
· OK, you want to hear my plan?
你知道我最喜欢计划了
- You know I always love a plan.
好 白宫有地下隧道
OK, so the White House has underground tunnels.
已经好多年了
They' ve been around for decades.
他们利用隧道往返公馆
They go to and from the Residence.
所以我们需要的就是找到隧道
So all we need to do is find a tunnel.
这可不是《国家宝藏》
- This isn't"National Treasure, "babe.
我已经查看过那些隧道了
I' ve already looked into those tunnels.
它们不是我们通过猜谜能进入的尘封洞穴
They' re not dusty caverns we access by solving riddles.
可是有着高安保的通道
They' re high security passageways,
里面都是武装警卫
crawling with armed guards.
你知道我特别喜欢你那些
well, you know I love it when you come up
有创意的办法吧
with creative solutions.
好吧 等我想到一个有创意的办法
Yeah, well, I Il let you know
来对付使用巫毒魔法杀人的娃娃时
when I think of a creative solution
我会告诉你的
for a killer doll wielding voodoo magic.
好吧
Yeah.
天 杰克 你就是个天才
Oh, my God. Jake, you’ re a genius.
我们之前怎么没想到呢
How come we didn't think about this sooner?
我们杀了恰吉好多次
We kill Chucky over and over.
但他总能复活 对吧
But he always comes back, right?
用普通方法杀他是没用的
- Killing him normally is useless.
如果 查尔斯·利·雷能操控魔法
If Charles Lee Ray can manipulate magic,
也许我们也能
maybe we can too.
是时候我们以其人之道还治其人之身了
It's time we give Chucky a taste of his own medicine,
用巫毒魔法
voodoo style.
我们要从何处着手呢
Well, where do we start?
我是说 要去哪呢
I mean, where do we go?
我们先在暗网上搜索巫毒
We start by searching for voodoo on the dark web.
如果我们把在这些网站上发帖的用户的元数据结合起来
If we combine the metadata of users who post on these sites,
找出它们的共同点
it'll isolate common denominators
我们就能找到
that lead us to the main- -
能不能说人话
- You want to say that in English?
是一位玄学专家 当然了
Oh, a metaphysical expert. Of course.
我们这就去找他
This is where we go.
他在乔治亚州 大概一天的车程
- He's in Georgia, about a day’ s drive away.
来个公路旅行吧
Road trip?
可咱俩都没有驾照
Neither of us have a driver’ s license.
开车应该没多难吧
Can't be that hard.
约瑟夫 你看上去好虚弱
Joseph, you look really sick.
是啊 我告诉你了 我就要死了
- Yeah, well, I told you, I' m dying.
你不能死 不能再死一次了
You can' t die, not again.
嘿 看着点儿
Hey, hey, watch itl
算了 随便吧
Oh, go ahead.
我想让你变好
- I want to make you feel better.
我觉得这不可能了 孩子
- I don' t think that's possible, kid.
你冷吗 我有你最喜欢的毯子
- Are you cold? I have your favorite blankie.
亨利
- Henry?
是被我的脸吓到了对吧
- It's my face, isn't it?
妈妈 是泰迪 他在我房间里
Mommy, it's Teddy! He's in my room!
什么 不 亲爱的 泰迪已经死了
- What? No. Sweetheart, no, Teddy is gone.
不 是真的
No, he’s real!
你又出现幻觉了
- It's just your big imagination again.
他看着我
Shh. - He looked at me.
想告诉我什么事
He was trying to tell me something.
求你去和他说说话 妈妈
Please go talk to him, Mommy.
好 好
OK, OK
我去看看
I'II go take a look, OK?
小心点 妈妈
Please, be careful, Mommy.
亨利
Oh, Henry.
现在我都硬不起来了
Now I can t even get it up.
简直太难堪了
This is so embarrassing.
是莱克西吗
- Was that Lexy?
不是
No.
好吧 是她
OK, yes.
但我不想回复她
But I' m not texting back.
我很确定我们已经结束了
I' m pretty sure it' s over.
初次约会现场死了十个人
I mean, when ten people die on your first date,
简直太煞风景了
it's kind of a mood killer.
更别提
On top of, you know- -
她根本对我不感兴趣
The fact that she wasn' t interested in me.
真抱歉
- I' m so sorry.
她道歉了 但是
- I mean, she apologized, but, like- -
格兰特
Grant,
有些时候 道歉是远远不够的
sometimes, the hard truth is that
这就是最残酷的事实
apologies just aren't enough.
一段感情需要的是信任
A relationship requires trust,
莱克西打破了你对她的信任
and Lexy broke yours.
对的人能够看到并欣赏真正的你
The right person will be able to see and appreciate
而不是这些外在的东西
who you are outside of all of this.
是啊
Yeah.
我想你是对的
Yeah, I guess you' re right.
别让她轻易操纵你的心绪
- Don't let her manipulate you.
好
Yeah.
妈 我知道了 我会小心
OK, Mom, I get it. Be careful.
我
- I- -
你不是应该帮我挡住跟踪者的吗
- Aren't you supposed to keep stalkers away from me?
可现在是谁在跟踪谁呢
Yeah, well, who’s stalking who in this scenario?
我只是想说 别再盯着她的短信了
Look, all I' m saying is, stop staring at her texts
直接去和她本人交流吧
and talk to the girl in person,
成熟一点
like a big boy.
这就对了
There you go.
嘿 格兰特
Hey, Grant.
莱克西
Hey, Lexy.
我想对派对上的事
- I wanted to offer my condolences
表示我的哀悼
for what happened at the party.
就这样吗
- Is that it?
我一直想联系上你
Been trying to get a hold of you.
听着
Look,
你也知道 我明白只是被人当作
you know I know how much it sucks
个些政治家的孩子有多糟糕
to be seen as just the kid of some politician,
你不知道你的朋友是喜欢你这个人
to wonder if your friends like you
还是看上了你的家族关系
or just your family connections.
-你话是这样说 可  -我还没说完
- You're saying that, but- - - I' m not finished.
对我来说 你不仅仅是总统儿子那么简单
To me, you' re more than just the First Son.
你性格幽默 又是个好哥哥
You’re funny and a good brother
出乎意料的是 跳舞也很好
and a surprisingly great dancer.
你也能理解
And you know what it' s like
经历过那些事情是什么感觉
to go through some serious shit.
失去你爱的人
To lose someone you love.
不是所有人都能理解
Not everyone understands that.
我不知道 我们之间是否可以
I don' t know, is there any way that we could just, like...
重新来过呢
start over?
嗨 我是格兰特
Hi. I' m Grant.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you. -
假装自己很受欢迎 却是个内心孤独之人
Pretend popular, actual loner.
你是我这么久以来
You’re the first person I' ve.
第一个
liked so much.
如此喜欢的人
Ever.
我也喜欢你
- I like you too.
格兰特
Grant
亨利娃娃的事
About Henry' s doll.
几年前卡洛琳也拥有过一个那样的娃娃
Caroline had the same doll a few years back, and- -
抱歉 先生
I' m sorry, sir.
马上要上课了
But homeroom is starting.
不如你们两个下次再约
Why don' t you two make a plan for another time?
好
Yeah, um...
你想下次再来
would you want to come over again
一起看看电影什么的吗
for, like, a movie night or something?
好啊 当然 这周末如何
- Yeah. Yeah, totally. Hows this weekend?
杰克和德文能一起来吗
Oh, and can Jake and Devon come too?
为什么
- Why?
我不觉得他们喜欢我
I don' t think they really like me.
当然喜欢了
Of course they do.
我喜欢你啊 他们是我的家人
I like you, and they' re my family.
好吧 我回头发信息给你
- AII right, I ll text you.
好了 跟我说说
OK, tell me about this
你沾上的这个诅咒 杰克
curse you contracted, Jake.
停
－ Stop.
你们来这干什么
Why are you here?
你知道这个娃娃吗
- Are you familiar with this doll?
我不能透露其他病患的信息
- I can' t disclose information on other patients.
-拜托  -等等
- Oh, come on. - Wait.
你是说恰吉是你的病人
So you' re saying Chucky' s one of your patients.
很不幸 作为一位医生
Unfortunately, as a physician,
我不能
I am una- - - Ah, ah, ah, ah.
别拿希波克拉底誓言那一套跟我们说事儿
Don't give us any bullshit about the Hippocratic Oath.
你的网站上写的清清楚楚
Your website clearly states
你发过的唯一誓言
that the only oath you' ve ever taken
是给你唯一的主 丹巴拉
is to your one true lord, Damballa.
好吧
Fine.
我是最近接诊的恰吉
I treated Charles recently.
-告诉我们怎么杀掉他  -你给他看的什么病
Tell us how to kill him. - Treated for what, exactly?
很抱歉 我还有其他
My apologies, but I have sick patients
真需要解除诅咒的病人
with actual curses to attend to.
求你了
- Please.
他杀了我们爱的所有人
He's killed everyone we' ve ever loved.
我妈 他爸
My mom, his dad,
还有之后收留我们的人
the woman who took us in after,
甚至杰克八岁的继弟
even Jake' s eight- year- old foster brother.
我们不能再这样下去了
- We can't live like this anymore.
罗森医生 救命
- Dr. Rosen, pleasel
我好痛苦
I' m in agony!
查尔斯就要死了
Charles is dying.
恰吉之前也死过
－ Chucky' s died before.
很多次
A lot.
但他死不了多久
He won t stay dead.
可以直接转移到新的躯体中
He'll just move into a new body
把死掉的躯壳抛之脑后
and leave the dying one behind.
我们得杀掉他的灵魂
We have to kill his soul,
这样恰吉才不会再复活过来
make it so Chucky can never come back again.
查尔斯的灵魂沾染了基督教的魔法
Charles' soul is tainted with Christian magic.
他提到过一个糟糕的驱魔仪式
He mentioned something about a botched exorcism that- -
原来是你们做的啊
- Ah, that was you guys.
就他目前的情况 是无法抵抗
Well, in his current state, he is unable to combat
深入骨髓的天主教癌症
the Catholic cancer that has taken root.
意思是
Meaning
意思就是他暂时还无法转移去其他躯体
Meaning he can' t jump to another vessel
直到这一痛苦的过程结束
until this affliction is expunged.
考虑到他目前的情况 以及
Considering his advanced state and the diminishing time
他没多少时间扭转局面
with which he has to reverse the situation,
就像我说过的 查尔斯就要死了
like I said, Charles is dying.
他很快会死
He's gonna die, soon,
但这不意味着他会彻底消失
which does not mean that he will cease to exist.
他的灵魂会到达鬼界
His soul will cross over to the spirit realm.
那恰吉到底是灵魂还是鬼魂
- Wait, so is Chucky a spirit or a soul?
灵魂 鬼魂 土豆和土豆有区别吗
- Spirit, soul. To- may- to, to- may- to.
-是土豆和马铃薯  -就是啊
- To- mah- to. - Exactly.
那我们怎么去鬼界
- Well, how do we get to the spirit realm?
死了就能去
By dying. Duh.
作为医生 我建议你们别再追着查尔斯不放了
As a physician, my advice is, pursue Charles no further.
这条路上等待你们的只有死亡和折磨
Only death and suffering await you on this path.
好走不送
Have a nice day.
詹姆斯
- James?
你怎么在家
- What are you doing home?
我还想问你呢
- I could ask you the same question.
-你还好吧  -我不好
Is everything OK? - No.
已经有一段时间了
No, things haven't been for some time now.
你什么意思
- What does that mean?
是亨利
It's Henry.
他对鬼魂和约瑟夫的痴迷
And his obsession with ghosts and Joseph.
我一直想和你谈谈这个
- I've been meaning to talk to you about that.
他说他在房间里看到了泰迪的鬼魂
He says he saw Teddy' S ghost in his bedroom.
我觉得他情况越来越糟了
I think he's getting worse.
我觉得泰迪的死
I- - I think Teddy' s death is bringing up
勾起了他对约瑟夫的感情
some unresolved feelings about Joseph and- -
夏洛特 我相信他说的
－ Charlotte, I believe him.
我看到约瑟夫了
I' ve seen Joseph.
詹姆斯
James.
在万圣节晚会上 我看到他了
- At the Halloween gala. I saw him.
不 詹姆斯 那是亨利的娃娃
No, James, that was Henry' s doll.
不 夏洛特 就是他
- No, Charlotte, it was him.
你为什么不告诉我
- Why didn' t you tell me?
我们曾经无话不说的
We used to tell each other everything.
我能怎么说
- What am I supposed to say?
我看到了鬼魂吗
That I see ghosts?
你现在不就在这样说吗
- Isn't that what you' re telling me now?
现在不一样了
- It’s different now
我很确定我看到的是真的
because I' m sure what I saw was real.
昨天的新闻发布会上
At the press conference yesterday,
约瑟夫又出现了
Joseph was there again.
他坐在那里盯着我
He sat there watching me.
他看着我 夏洛特
He was watching me, Charlotte,
提醒着我有多失败
reminding me of all my failures.
不 你没有失败
Oh, no, you haven' t failed.
约瑟夫生病了
Joseph was sick.
你做什么也救不回他了
There's nothing any of us could have done to save him.
还记得施耐德医生在治疗时说的话吗
Remember what Dr. Schneider said in therapy?
有时候我们的大脑
You know, sometimes our mind finds ways
会想办法帮助我们克服哀伤
of helping us cope with our grief.
别用这套说辞对付我 夏洛特
Don't do this to me. Charlotte.
-别把我当小孩子哄  -或许你只是
Don't treat me like a child. - But maybe you just need
-需要休息一下  -我知道我看到了什么
some rest. - I know what I saw.
我看到了我们的儿子
I saw our son.
告诉我是我疯了
Tell me I' m going crazy.
说是我神智不清了
Tell me I' m losing my mind.
你来向我解释 因为我也想弄清楚
Explain it to me because I' m trying to understand,
你明白吗
you know?
你觉得我就是无情无义吗
- Do you think I' m heartless?
难道我就不为约瑟夫感到哀伤吗
That I don' t mourn Joseph too?
只有你和亨利因为失去了他
That you and Henry are the only ones
心里出现了无法填补的空缺吗
with a hole inside you where he used to be?
我每天都在想他
I think about him every day.
每次我走过他的房间
Every time I walk past his room,
每次看到他的东西
find something of his,
或是看着我们的儿子
or watch our boys struggle to grow up
成长路上再也没有弟弟的陪伴
without their baby brother, I- -
可我不能沉湎太久
I can' t dwell on that.
为了家庭 我也必须坚强起来
I have to be strong for our family.
如果你要再去找施耐德医生
If you need to see Dr. Schneider again
帮你面对自己的伤痛 我可以帮你安排
to help you cope with our loss, I can arrange that.
但我要你
But I need you- - -
我要你振作起来
- I need you to get a hold of yourself.
这个家庭不能只靠我一个人来维系
I cannot be the only one keeping this family together,
不能再这样了
not alone and not anymore.
你怎么能这样 你做了什么
How could you? What have you done?
瞧瞧你干的好事
You've done this.
妈妈现在得走了
Mommy has to go now.
你得当个好孩子
And you have to be a good boy.
真是他妈的是个笑话
- What a fucking joke.
因为你答应过我们
Because you promised us.
这位老兄呢
And this one?
他连特许经营权都没拿到
He didn' t even get a franchise.
好吧 小心夜幕降临
*AII right, all right, look out, night*
-天哪 不  -你在干什么
- Oh, God, no. - What are you doing?
愤怒的眼神
*Angry eyes*
一个眼神可以让你动弹不得
*One look from him can paralyze*
看得我想死
Kill me now.
让恐怖行者好好打你的脸
*Creeper done slap right cross your face*
那个小贱人
That little bitch!
她偷了我的招牌动作
She stole my moves.
去你妈的小婊砸
Fuck you, Ma- three- gan.
保安呢
Security!
在我身后 卡特勒监狱牢不可破的
Within the impenetrable walls of the Cutler unit
用
牢房里
just behind me,
女星詹妮弗·蒂莉目前已在狱中等待
actress Jennifer Tilly is currently on death row,
死刑执行
awaiting execution.
哦 蒂莉
Oh, Tiff.
谁能想到这一切会这样结束
Who would' ve thought it would all end like this?
医生很确信
- The doctor was pretty convinced
我们会害死自己的
we were gonna get ourselves killed.
是 可他又不了解我们
- Yeah, well, he doesn't know us.
反正我们活了这么久了
I mean, we survived this long, anyways.
似乎总有一天它会追上我们的
- It just seems like it' s gonna catch up to us someday.
我还有很多事情要做
There are so many things I still want to do,
尤其是和你在一起做
especially with you.
是吗
- Oh, yeah?
比如呢
Like what?
你懂的
You know
反正我们也要到很晚才能到家
- I mean, we' re not gonna get back until late anyway.
是
- True.
你有什么想法吗
You have something in mind?
放松 别这么做
*Relax, don't do it*
当你情难自已
*When you want to go to it*
放松 别这么做
*Relax, don't do it*
当你干柴烈火
* When you want to come*
放松 别这么做
* Relax, don't do it*
当你想翻云覆雨
* When you want to suck it, chew it*
放松 别这么做
* Relax, don't do it*
当你想巫山云雨
* When you want to come*
当你想男欢女爱
放松 放松 别这么做
*Relax, relax, don't do it*
当你想耳鬓厮磨
* When you want to go it*
放松 放松 别这么做
* Relax, relax, don't do it*
当你想宽衣解带
* When you want to come*
当你想颠龙倒凤
当你想鱼水之欢
* When you want to come*
来吧
*Come*
一次 就一次 嘿嘿嘿
*One time, one time, one time, hey! *
太爽了
－ That was awesome.
是吧
I know.
来吧
*Come*
埃利奥 埃利奥
Elio, Elio, Elio.
奥利弗 奥利弗
－ Oliver, Oliver- -
等等 叫我的名字
wait, call me by my name.
德文 德文 德文
- Devon, Devon, Devon.
这样好多了
- That’s better.
我永远都不想离开这个房间
- I never want to leave this room.
我也是
Me neither.
感觉不一样了
- I feel different.
是感觉好的那种不一样
Good different.
我也有同感
- I feel the same.
就像
It's like- -
别说 听起来会很傻的
no, it' s- - it' s gonna sound stupid.
不
No.
我觉得现在离你更亲近了
I feel closer to you now,
好像没有什么能把我们分开
like nothing can ever come between us.
我知道 我知道 这听起来很俗气
I know itI know it- - it sounds cheesy.
我也有同感
- I feel the same.
我爱你
- I love you.
我更爱你 德文
- I love you more, Devon.
不可能的
- That’ s not possible.
阳光普照
*Sunshine*
你去过加州吗
- Uh, you ever been to California?
没有
No.
我一直想去
- I' ve always wanted to go.
也许等这一切都结束了
I mean, maybe when this is all over,
我们可以来一次全国旅行
we can go on a- like a cross- country trip.
去每个州玩一遍 比如内布拉斯加州
Visit every state, like Nebraska.
内布拉斯加州有什么呢
I mean, what’ s even in Nebraska?
当然 我们可以这么干
- Yeah, sure. Yeah, we could do that.
如果这一切还能结束
If this is ever over.
你还好吗
- You OK?
没事
Fine.
怎么了
- What’s going on?
只是
Just- -
我们并不非得回去 你知道吗
we don't have to go back, you know?
我们现在就可以去旅行
We can still go on that trip, now.
德文
Devon. -
就像医生说的那样恰吉快死了
Chucky' s dying like the doctor said.
我们可以一起逃走
We can run away together.
不再等了
No more waiting.
我们别管了
Let’ s be done with it.
我害怕 如果你回去了
I'm afraid if you go back- -
杰克 我不能失去你
Jake, I can' t lose you.
德文 你知道我们不能丢下莱克西
Devon, you know we can't leave Lexy.
-她是我们的家人  -不 这我懂
I mean, she’ s our family. - No, I know.
但是她可以和我们一起走 我们可以说服她
But she can come with us. I think we could convince her- -
我知道你很害怕
- I know you' re scared.
我也是
I am too.
我们是英雄 我们是活到大结局的人
We're the heroes. We’re the final girls.
我们是他妈奥斯卡得主杰米·李·柯蒂斯
I mean, we’ re Jamie Lee fucking Oscar- winning Curtis.
这次我们会赢的 好吗
And we’ re gonna win this time, OK?
好吧
Right.
让我们结束这一切
Let’ s finish this.
我曾经拥有过一切
*I had it all*
阳光普照
*Sunshine*
呼唤着阳光
*Calling for the sunshine*
我再也受不了了
- I can' t do this anymore.
我得告诉詹姆斯真相 所有的真相
I need to tell James the truth, all of it.
你知道不能这么做 夏洛特
- You know you can't do that, Charlotte,
我们干了那么多事 不能回头了
not after everything we' ve done.
我想问一下 是什么让你突然改变主意的吗
May I ask what brought on this sudden change of heart?
詹姆斯快要疯了
James is losing his mind.
亨利也是
So is Henry.
他们觉得自己见鬼了 真他妈的
They think they' re seeing ghosts, for fuck' s sake.
这都是我的错
And it’ s all my fault.
我不是在保护我的家人 我是在毁他们
I am not protecting my family. I am destroying them.
可能詹姆斯跟你说的话里有些是真的
－ There may be some truth to what James told you.
开什么玩笑
- Oh, are you kidding me?
夏洛特 别这样
Charlotte, please. -
听我解释
Let me explain.
没有证据 没有线索
No evidence, no leads.
一个杀手是怎么进入白宫
How does a killer enter the White House,
这个世界上最安全的地方呢
the most secure place in the world,
还杀了十几个人
and murder over a dozen people?
这是个好问题
That is a good question,
你应该去弄清楚这个问题的答案
and one that you were supposed to figure out.
答案很清楚了
－ The answer is clear.
我不认为我们要对付的是一个政治刺客
I don' t think we re dealing with a political assassin
或者连环杀手
or a serial killer.
我们要对付的是某种超自然的东西
What we’ re dealing with is something supernatural.
万圣节晚会的录像
The footage from the Halloween gala
显示你的儿子约瑟夫
shows your son Joseph- -
你是想把谋杀罪名甩给
Oh, you want to pin the murders
一个失踪的孩子和一个鬼魂吗
on a disappearing kid, on a ghost?
看
Look.
蒂莉小姐
Miss Tilly?
又是他
It's him again.
他不停地打电话
He won’ t stop calling.
你可以走了
- You can go now.
-嘿 宝贝  -恰吉
Hey, doll. - Chucky.
我说了 我不想和你说话
I said I didn' t want to talk to you.
哪怕这是你最后的机会吗
- Even if it' s your last chance?
你在说什么
- What are you talking about?
我才是等着被执行死刑的人
I' m the one on death row.
我打开新闻 结果你住进白宫了
I turn on the news, and you' re at the White House,
在外面上步步高升
moving up in the world
而我却被关在牢里等死
while I' m stuck here behind bars to rot.
我要死了 小蒂
- I' m dying, Tiff.
好吧
OK, well
你复活之后给我打电话吧
call me when you resurrect.
到那时我可能已经离开这里了
I may be out of here by then.
不 我不会复活了
No, I m not gonna be resurrecting.
这次不会了
Not this time.
不 这次对我来说是在地下长眠
No, it’ s the long dirt nap for me,
大件事
the big enchilada.
我要死了
I'm a fucking goner.
你在说什么
- What are you talking about?
我把丹巴拉给惹了
- I screwed things up with Damballa,
没法支付精神魔法账单了
didn't pay the spiritual power bill,
现在魔法已经吹灯拔蜡了
and now it' s lights out.
不
No.
不 恰吉你是个小强
No, Chucky, you’re a cockroach.
你总是会复活的
You always come back.
这次不行了
Not this time.
你应该看看我的样子
You should see me.
我都秃了
I'm bald.
我已经枯萎了
I' m withered.
我好像还看到了黄褐斑
I think I saw a liver spot on my- -
别说了 恰吉
· Stop it, Chucky.
别说了 太恶心了
Stop it. That’s disgusting.
最糟糕的是
Worst part is,
在经历所有的杀戮刺激之后
after all the kills and all the thrills,
到最后
here at the end,
我甚至不知道这一切都是为了什么
I' m not even sure what it was all for.
不 恰吉
No, Chucky.
你有一段精彩的人生
You've lived a great life.
你还终结了很多人的人生
And you' ve ended so many more.
你知道吗 恰吉
You know, Chucky,
不管这一切 不管多少次
despite everything, despite all the times
我们把对方开膛破肚
we've tried to disembowel each other,
你还是那个我深爱的
you're still the brilliant psychopath
聪明绝顶的变态
I fell in love with.
你永远都是
And you always will be.
我也爱你 小蒂
- I love you too, Tiff.
那三个小淘气要来找我了
Those three brats are gonna be coming for me.
我想我还是认输吧
I think I' m gonna just throw in the towel.
振作起来
Pull yourself together.
你是杀手娃娃恰吉
You're Chucky the Killer Doll.
永远不要让他们忘记你是谁
Don't you ever let them forget who you are.
难道你不想作为史上最伟大的
Don't you want to go down in history
连环杀手被载入史册吗
as the greatest serial killer of all time?
想想你在哪里 恰吉
Think of where you are, Chucky.
你他妈在白宫
You’ re at the fucking White House!
要我说 死也要死得轰轰烈烈
I say, go out in a blaze of glory
杀一个够本 杀两个赚一个
and take as many as you can with you on the way out.
史上最伟大的 是吧
- The greatest of all time, huh?
你知道吗 娃娃脸
You know what, doll face?
你是对的
You're right.
你说得完全正确
You're absolutely right.
爸爸
Daddy.
Daddy!
爸爸
Daddy.
约瑟夫
- Joseph?
爸爸
Daddy.
约瑟夫
Joseph.
爸爸小心
Daddy, look outl
我玩的很开心哦 总统先生
- It's been fun, Mr. President.
但接下来就由我接手了
But I ll take it from here.
真是辉煌的瞬间哈
Blaze of glory, huh?
试试整个地狱如何
How about the whole fucking inferno?